翻译: Michael PiPi Reginamoon
翻译:   Z小花儿 Silence 小僵僵
翻译:  SophiaSaaaga  Malinowskee
校对:   Z小花儿 Michael  肉松
时间轴:  Jenny  chance-coco
后期&特效:  咖啡・Lee    总监： 苹果果
第一时间下载无删减美剧  必须登录字幕组网站www.zimuzu.tv
www.zimuzu.tv  更好更快的原创翻译 双语字幕
我是奥利弗・奎恩
My name is Oliver Queen.
五年里  我被困在地狱
After 5 years in hell,
我回来只有一个目标
I returned home with only one goal--
拯救我的城市
to save my city.
现在我有两个身份
Today, I fight that war on two fronts.
白天  我是星城的市长
By day, I lead star city as its mayor,
而晚上  我是另一个人
but by night, I am someone else.
我是另一个存在
I am something else.
我就是绿箭侠
I am the Green Arrow.
《绿箭》前情提要
Previously on "Arrow"...
前警察队长昆汀・兰斯
Former police captain Quentin Lance,
他将任副市长辅助我
who will be serving beside meas.
非常感谢您的信任  市长先生
Appreciate the vote of confidence, mr. Mayor.
你不是星城来的吗
Are you not from Star City?
不是  是海文洛克
No. Havenrock.
有些事你要知道
There's something that I need you to know.
海文洛克并不是原定目标
Havenrock was not the intended target.
有人为了减少伤亡数量改变了
Someone redirected the missile to reduce
导弹的方向
the number of casualties.
这个人就是我
That someone was me.
从我杀安迪到现在
Ever since I killed Andy...
你觉得你需要被惩罚吗
You think you need to be punished.
别再为我费劲了  莱拉
Stop fighting for me, Lyla.
我们要谈谈约翰
We need to talk about John.
他回国了  在监狱里
He's back in the country, and he's in prison,
我需要你把他弄出来
And I need you to break him out.
快点  奥林匹亚先生  赶紧的
Come on, Mr. Olympia. Hustle up.
奥林匹亚先生是健美比赛的冠军
Mr. Olympia's a bodybuilding competition.
我以前  现在是奥林匹克运动员
I was--am an Olympic athlete.
是吗  现在时不时努力了就能拿金牌
Yeah? They give out gold medals for effort now?
真有趣  不过我拿的是铜牌
Very funny, and it was a bronze medal.
有那么难记住吗
Why is that so hard to remember?
闭嘴  每次执行任务的时候
Quiet. Every time you're out in the field,
都有可能送命
you could die.
别忘了这一点  集中精神
Don't forget that, don't lose focus.
守望者  找到目标了吗
Overwatch, do we have the target?
正向东出口移动  速度很快
Headed toward the east exit, closing fast.
知道他偷了什么吗
Do we know what he stole?
还不知道  不过我有预感
Not yet, but I have a feeling
我们很快就会知道了
we're about to find out.
前提是我们把他拦在警戒线
Only if we snag him in the cordon.
阿耳特弥斯  准备好
Artemis, be ready.
我这次真的可以射人了吗
Does this mean I actually get to shoot someone?
不是  我不是那个意思
I mean, not, you know, shoot someone shoot someone.
我是说除了...
I just meant that more than--
我们知道你的意思
We know what you meant.
你们要等他到达警戒线
You wait for him to reach the cordon,
然后再动手
then engage.
-明白了吗  -明白
- Do you copy? - Copy.
-明白  -明白
- Copy. - Copy.
可是范围挺大的
Still a lot of ground to cover.
应该让破烂王也来
Rags should be here.
守望者  你知道破烂王的情况吗
Overwatch, do you have a 20 on Ragman?
我给他发了大概十条短信
I texted him, like, 10 times
然后又发了十条  都没回复
and then 10 more, but nada.
他可能病了
Maybe he's sick.
最近有流感
I mean, the flu's been going around,
而且从他那些破布来看
And by the looks of those rags,
他不怎么经常洗衣服
he does not hit the drycleaner very often.
你好啊  帅哥[西语]
Hola, muchacho.
野狗  让阿耳特弥斯动手
Wild Dog, that is Artemis' shot.
我能搞定
I got him.
搞什么
What the?
交给我
I got him.
科尔德实业
我刚才怎么说的
What did I say?
让阿耳特弥斯动手
That was Artemis' shot!
这家伙差点跑掉
Dude was getting away.
不  没有
No, he wasn't.
而你失手了
And you missed.
你以前是海军
You were in the navy.
不应该表现得这么差
You should know better.
其实我是被开除军籍的
I was dishonorably discharged actually.
你以为我不知道吗
You think that I don't know that?
科尔德实业
把那家伙和证据
Deliver that and the evidence
交给打击罪案小组  然后回家
to the Anti-Crime Unit and then go home.
那今晚的训练课呢
What about tonight's training session?
你们休息几天
You're taking a few days off.
你又一次"干得好"
Nice going... again.
我们怎么把这家伙送到打击罪案小组
How are we supposed to get this guy to the ACU,
叫优步吗
call a Uber?
绿  箭
第五季 第四集
奥利弗
Oliver.
行动都结束  你已经失联好几天了
The op's over, and you've been MIA for days.
这是不可接受的
It's not acceptable.
赶快振作起来
Get it together immediately,
否则你就滚蛋
or you're off the team.
我来就是为了这个
That's why I'm here,
亲口告诉你
to tell you in person.
我退出了
I'm off the team.
这么快就认输了
Feels pretty quick to throw in the towel.
你不是说才刚开始吗
I thought you were just getting started.
是的  可后来费利西蒂
I was, and then Felicity
跟我说了她对海文洛克所做的事
told me the truth about her role in Havenrock.
你不知道她告诉我了吗
You didn't know she told me.
她有没有跟你说她当时面对
Did she also tell you that she was faced
两难的选择
with an impossible choice?
我完全明白
I completely realize that.
我知道那不是她的错
I get it wasn't her fault,
可是这无法改变
but that doesn't change the fact
我每次看到她的时候
that every time I look at her
都会想起我的家人
I see the faces of my family,
所有我所爱的人
of everyone I ever loved.
见到费利西蒂我就不断想起
Felicity is a constant reminder
我所失去的  只要是这种情况
of what I lost, and as long as that's true,
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不能待在这里
I can't be here.
那你父亲呢
What about your father?
你不是因为他才做这些的吗
I thought he was the reason you were doing this.
我会找到其他办法去纪念他的
I'll have to find another way to honor him.
我很遗憾留不住你
I'm sorry to lose you.
我很遗憾要走
I'm sorry to go.
之前的一切都谢谢你
Thank you for everything.
我是听错了还是
Did my comms deceive me,
你真的让新人去星城警局庆祝胜利了
or did you actually let the recruits take an SCPD victory lap.
哪来的庆祝胜利
It's never a victory lap.
他们现在能力还不足
They're rough around the edges,
不过除了罗里大家都在进步
But they're making progress except Rory,
他当时在楼上等我
who was waiting for me upstairs
跟我说他要退出
to say that he quit.
他说你告诉他海文洛克的事了
He said you spoke with him about Havenrock.
你还好吗
How you holding up?
她不知道吗
She doesn't know?
约翰入狱的事吗  奥利弗跟我说了
About John being in prison? Oliver told me.
我很为你难过
I'm so sorry.
莱拉的意思是
What Lyla means--
我们要把他救出来
we are gonna break him out.
从军事监狱里救出来
Of military prison?
-没错  -等等  那之后怎么办
- Yep. - Wait, and then what?
约翰后半辈子就要做个逃犯吗
John is just a fugitive for the rest of his life?
那也总比无辜受罚强
Better than being punished for something he didn't do.
莱拉  我在研究你给我的安保图纸
Lyla, I've been studying the schematics that you hooked me up with.
如果约翰配合  就容易很多
This would be a lot easier if we had John's cooperation.
朗豪军事监狱  安保系统
原始图纸 入口
现在这是什么情况
You don't have what now?
显然  和回到老婆孩子身边相比
Apparently, prison is more appealing to John
约翰对蹲监狱更感兴趣
than coming home to his own wife and child.
好  等等
Ok. So wait a minute.
现在不仅你们想犯下多项重罪
Not only do you want to commit multiple felonies
让约翰后半生都变成逃犯
and make John a wanted man for the rest of his life,
而且他根本就不想跟你们走
he doesn't actually want you to?
我能和你谈谈吗
Can I speak with you for a minute?
好
Yeah.
她这边有问题吗
Is she going to be a problem?
没有  但是
No, but...
我还想让她帮忙呢
I was counting on her being a help.
或许我该找几个我的特工来
Maybe I should pull a few of my agents in on this.
不行  如果这事留下你的痕迹
No. If this--if this has your fingerprints on it,
那小约翰的父母就都变成犯人了
then both of John Jr.'s parents will be fugitives.
可能有样东西能助我们成功
There is something that might actually make this not impossible.
我刚读了一项新科技的简介
I just read a briefing memo on a new piece of tech,
一种反键分子化合物
An antimolecular compound.
我本想让费利西蒂帮我们搞到手的
I was kind of hoping Felicity could help us get our hands on it.
莱拉  无论那是什么  我来搞定
Lyla, whatever it is, I'll handle it.
二次测试完成
Second test over.
别弄得比拆线还严重就行
Do not make any worse by pulling out suture.
安纳托利  如果兄弟会就这样对新成员
Anatoly, if this is how the Bratva treat their new members,
我可不愿想象他们怎么对待敌人
I'd hate to see how they treat their enemies.
通过第三次和最终测试  就明白了
Pass third and final test, find out.
测试内容是什么
What's the test?
你一直在问科瓦的事
You keep asking about Kovar.
我们的线人说他能让你更接近答案
Our sources say this man will get you one step closer.
不过你得快点
You have to act fast, though.
他早上就要被提审了
He will be arraigned in morning.
提审
Arraigned?
-被抓了  -懂了
- Jail. - Yeah
可你怎么知道他会告诉我
But what makes you think he'll talk to me.
信任是相互的
You trust me. I trust you.
现在喝酒还太早了吧  你觉得呢
Look. It's a little early for a drink, don't you think?
这不是让你喝的
It's not for drinking.
安纳托利  你这是干什么
Anatoly, what the hell was that for?
一边去
傻逼酒鬼
我是不是应该提前录好迟到的道歉
I should probably just start prerecording apologies for being late.
没事  西娅告诉我们了
Don't worry. Thea told us.
我很遗憾  哥们  痛风太难缠了
I'm sorry, man. Gout is a bitch.
可不是吗
Yes, it is.
其实我想休假好好治疗一下
I'm actually gonna be taking some time off to have it taken care of.
好在现在有了副市长
Well, fortunately, we now have
可以帮忙挑这个重担
a deputy mayor to help pick up the slack.
和你共事一定很愉快
It'll be great working with you.
你的职业生涯很令人钦佩  兰斯先生
You've had an impressive career, Mr. Lance?
是把  现在外面很多人
Yeah. I mean, a lot of people out there
可能没这么想
probably wouldn't, uh, share that opinion.
不过谢谢你
But thank you.
当人民公仆不容易啊
Public service isn't easy.
有时清除污秽也会脏及自身
Sometimes, you get a little dirty clearing out the filth.
说起这个  我听说昨晚逮捕了一个人
Speaking of which, I heard there was an arrest last night
或许能在托拜厄斯・丘奇案上帮到我们
that may help in our case against Tobias Church.
是塞吉奥・埃斯皮诺萨  洛斯・阿尔的孔长期同伙
Sergio Espinosa, long-time Los Halcones member
后来成了丘奇的左膀右臂
Turned Church strongman.
绿箭侠和他调皮的治安维护者
The Green Arrow and his merry band of vigilantes
把他当礼物送给了打击罪案小组
left him gift-wrapped for us at anti-crime.
就差个蝴蝶结了
The only thing that was missing was a bow.
你听起来好像不太开心
Well, you don't sound to happy about that.
治安维持者只能暂时解决问题
Vigilantes are a superficial solution.
如果还得靠他们来帮我们维持治安
If we need their help to get our streets clean--
就代表了我们的工作还不到位
It means we haven't done our jobs right.
你觉得你能让埃斯皮诺萨供出丘奇吗
Do you think that you can get Espinosa to flip on Church?
我会给他施压  看他会不会妥协
I'll lean on him hard, see if he buckles.
你要确保不会有什么腐败警察包庇他
Make sure he doesn't get any help from crooked cops.
不可能的
Not a chance.
我会亲自查看保管链上的每一个证据
I'm gonna walk every piece of evidence in the custody chain through myself.
很好  假如你没意见的话
Good. Uh, if it's all right with you,
我会让昆汀协助你
I'll have Quentin accompany you,
我不在的时候就让他做我的眼睛和耳朵
be my eyes and ears while I'm out of town.
当然没意见
Sure.
给我们点时间让我们熟悉彼此
Give us a little bit of time to get acquainted.
好极了
Great.
抱歉  但从什么时候起我的职责里
I'm sorry. When did, uh, babysitting evidence
还包括了保护证据
become part of the job description?
我信任你
Since I trust you.
真的吗
You do?
在发生了所有一切之后
I mean, all things considered?
如果我们不觉得你是这份工作的好人选
If we didn't think you were right for the job,
我们怎么会对你发出邀请呢  是吧
we wouldn't have offered it to you, right?
我这一周都滴酒未沾
I haven't had a drink in a week, ok?
说起来你到底要去哪里
Where the hell are you going anyway?
这时候度假有点奇怪吧
Strange time for a vacation.
并不是去度假
You should probably assume that it's not a vacation.
我该问吗
Should I even ask?
不该  我不会离开很久的
No. I--I'm not gonna be gone long.
拜托你们确保一下
Just please make sure
我不在的期间没人毁了这座城市就好
that no one destroys the city while I'm away.
没问题
Sure.
好吧
OK.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
重新查看星城警局的证物记录
Reviewing the SCPD evidence log
查看我们昨晚
on what we kept from getting stolen
帮科尔德实业保住的东西
from Kord Industries last night.
-6800处理器  -然后呢
- 6,800 processor. - So?
没错  科尔德从事尖端科技
Exactly. Kord manufactures bleeding-edge tech,
军用级别的武器
military-grade weapons,
里面有这么多足以毁灭城市的东西
I mean, all kinds of city-threatening items.
为什么丘奇却让人去偷一个
Why would Church send a guy to steal a computer chip
科技商店就能买到的电脑芯片
That you could buy from any tech village store?
管他呢  所有东西都要被锁起来了
Well, who cares? Everything's on its way to lockup now.
因为丘奇的最后一步
Because knowing what Church's endgame was
让我觉得这事儿并没有结束  还在蛰伏
is like--it's like this thing that's still out there, lurking.
你还好吧
You all right over there?
因为我一直说个不停  你却一言不发
Because I've been doing a lot of talking, and you haven't,
很奇怪啊
which is very weird.
你还记得你让我告诉罗里海文洛克的真相吗
You know how you told me to tell Rory about Havenrock?
是啊
Yeah.
他并不是得流感请假了是吧
Oh! He's not sick with the flu, is he?
嗯  他只是受不了和我共事
No. He's just sick of working with me.
你有试着和他谈谈吗
Did you try talking to him?
他全家人都死了
There's not a lot I can say
我说什么都没办法让他好过一点吧
that would make him feel OK about his entire family being killed.
有消息
Incoming.
又一起抢劫发生在...
Another robbery in progress at--
帕尔默科技  我得打电话给奥利弗
Palmer Tech! I got to call Oliver.
警报 发生劫案
帕尔默科技
或许不该打  就让他们被抢
Or maybe don't, and we'll just let them get robbed.
报丹尼斯先生解雇我们之仇
It will serve Mr. Dennis right for firing us.
他只炒了我  你是自己辞职的
He fired me. You quit.
因为他炒了你  没差啦
Because he fired you. Same thing.
桑切斯  你那有发现吗
Sanchez, you got anything?
没有
Nada.
怎么了
What's up?
有人闯进帕尔默科技了
There's been a break-in at Palmer Tech.
你还在那片吗
Are you still in the area?
在  我可以去看看
Yeah. I can look into that.
帕尔默科技怎么样了
How was Palmer Tech?
在你回答之前
Before you answer,
你要意识到你的手机是有定位的
you should consider that your phone has GPS,
假如你还想撒谎的话
and if you were thinking about lying,
那我佩服你前后说法的一致性
I do admire your consistency.
我没想着骗你
I wasn't thinking of lying to you.
我只是不想把你牵扯进来
I wasn't looping you in
毕竟你明确表示过你不赞成这个决定
after you made it clear you didn't approve of the decision.
是约翰自己不赞成这个计划
John is the one who doesn't approve of the plan.
约翰现在不理智
John's not thinking clearly.
我赌罗伊是理智的  假如他在这里的话
Well, I bet Roy is, and if he were here,
我觉得他会告诉你
I think he would tell you
逃亡的生活根本不算生活
that life on the run is no life at all,
而且我似乎记得你是不赞成那个计划的
and I seem to remember you not being on board with that plan.
罗伊当时在做一个错误的选择
Roy was making a bad choice
和约翰现在一样
just like John is making a bad choice.
他如今因为一个他没犯过的罪
He is currently locked up in a military prison
而被关在军事监狱里
for a crime he didn't commit.
那是为他之前犯的罪赎过  这有什么错呢
To atone for a crime that he did commit, and what does it matter?
约翰自己不想走
John doesn't want to leave.
这不应该由你来决定
It is not your choice.
为什么你老是去替他做出选择
Why do you always have to go and make decisions for him?
他已经抛弃这个团队了
He already abandoned the team.
我不能让他再抛弃他的家庭
I am not gonna let him abandon his family.
是因为这个吗
Is that what this is about,
因为约翰离开了团队
John leaving the team?
这事很简单
This is simple.
我要阻止约翰做出他一定会后悔的决定
I am gonna stop John from making a decision he will come to regret.
你应该考虑一下对罗里做同样的事情
You should consider doing the exact same thing with Rory.
你意识到我和罗里谈谈话的性质
You do realize that me having a chat with Rory
完全不同于你去犯几个重罪吧
is completely different than you committing half a dozen felonies, right?
你有想到你会再次干这种事吗
Did you ever think you'd be doing this again,
处理证据
handling evidence?
没有  我也没想到我会成为副市长
No. Didn't think I'd be deputy mayor either,
然后就成了如今这样
But here we are.
老实说  我很惊讶你居然接受了
I was surprised you took the job, to be honest.
我听说  你和奎恩有着...
From what I hear, you and Queen have a, uh--
复杂的过往
a complicated history.
一定得放下很多前嫌吧
Got to be a lot of hatchets to bury there.
是啊  起码我知道我是如何放下的
Yeah. Well, at least I know where they're buried.
那是买不来也偷不走的东西
That's something you can't buy or steal.
东西到了  老大
Package is here, boss.
地方检察官和副市长也来了
D.A., deputy mayor, too.
赠品呗
Bonus.
准备好行动
Get ready to move.
我猜猜  费利西蒂跟你们说的
Let me guess. Felicity filled you in.
说你打算闯进军事监狱吗
That you're gonna break into a military prison?
对  而你还好意思叫我野狗
Yeah, and you got the nerve to call me Wild Dog?
不想再争论这事
I'm done debating this.
真的吗  因为我们还是头一次听说
Really? Because this is the first we've heard of it.
还以为我们是团队
I thought we were your team.
一个人跑去劫狱
Running off to bust someone out of prison
是队友干的事吗
sounds like team business,
你被抓了  我们会怎样
And what happens to us when you get caught?
你说得很清楚了
You've made it clear that
有你在  我们才能当治安维护者
we can't do this vigilante thing without you.
等我被抓了  我不会被抓的
When I get caught? I'm not gonna get caught.
对  因为我们不会放你那么做
Right because we're not gonna let you do this.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你是说你们不会放我走吗
Did you say that you're not gonna let me?
对  我得看着你亲自把证物存好了
Yes. I need to see you physically deposit the item.
我干这活有十五年了
I've been on this job 15 years.
从没弄丢一份证据
I've never lost a piece of evidence.
别有压力  警官
Now relax, sergeant.
我们不是怀疑你的专业能力
No one's doubting your proficiency here, ok?
像是怀疑
Seems like.
好了
This is it.
我可以开始干活了吗
You gonna let me do my job now?
开始吧
Have at it.
科尔德实业
什么情况
What the hell?
快出去
Get out of here!
去找武器  伙计们
Find the weapons, boys.
抱歉  先生们
Sorry, gents.
装上武器
Load them up!
然后把这里炸掉
And burn this puppy down.
走  快走
Let's go, let's go!
好了
OK.
最后机会
Last chance.
别挡道
Get off the street.
没想到他真的对你们动手了
I didn't think he'd actually hit you guys.
你知道最操蛋的是什么吗
You know what really sucks?
发现之前所有的训练中
Realizing that in all those training sessions
他虽然把我们揍了个遍
where he was kicking our respective asses
但他还是有所保留
the whole time he was taking it easy on us.
对  也提醒我
Yeah. Remind me to never, ever
绝对不要惹毛他
get on his bad side.
我想也就是说他有温柔的一面
I think that would imply that he has a good side,
费利西蒂  麻烦你再解释一下
And, you know, Felicity, could you please explain to me again
你怎么觉得这样能行得通
how you thought this was all gonna go down?
我原以为如果看到你们团结一致
Well, I thought if he saw you guys all united
反对他的疯狂计划  他就会三思
against his crazy plan he'd reconsider.
对哦  因为都知道奥利弗・奎恩
Right because Oliver Queen is known
会三思后行  听取别人的意见呢
for thinking things through and taking input from others.
好
Right.
这里越来越人丁兴旺了
The ever-expanding club house.
你是谁
And who are you?
我是西娅  奥利弗的幕僚长
I'm Thea, Oliver's Chief of Staff.
也是他的妹妹
And also his sister.
被跟我说奥利弗也揍你
Don't tell me Oliver beat you up, too,
奥利干的
Ollie did this?
实战教学  说来话长
Object lesson, long story.
没事  别提了
It's fine. Don't ask.
你怎么了
What happened to you?
托拜厄斯・丘奇干的
Tobias Church happened.
你们从科尔德实业那找到的证据
That evidence that you guys recovered from Kord Industries--
被改成了炸弹
Modified to go boom.
是他要把东西收藏起来的
He wanted it to be put into lockup.
他还想抢劫
And he wanted to raid it.
一次性解决武器问题
One-stop shopping for weapons.
还包括从艾美科技那偷走的火箭筒
Including those RPGs that he took from AmerTek
如果报告无误的话
If this report's right.
事故报告
事故总结
我们得弄清他打算
We got to find out what he's planning
用这些武器干什么  肯定图谋不轨
to do with those weapons--because it ain't nothing good.
奥利弗真不该这个时候出城
This is a really bad time for Oliver to be out of town.
我试过联系他了  没音讯
Yeah. I just tried him. He's gone dark.
你们不如出去打听一下
Why don't you guys hit the streets?
趁还来得及  得赶紧弄清
We want to figure out what Church is up to
丘奇有什么打算
before it's too late.
你确定
You sure?
我想奥利弗不愿让我们单独执行任务
I don't think Oliver would want us out there without him.
对  奥利弗不在  他就无权干涉
Right. Well, Oliver forfeited his opinion when he left.
好  所以现在得全员出动
OK, but this is an all hands on deck situation,
伤员也得出动
rag-covered hands included.
我就说说
Just saying.
美国军人惩戒所交货处
大兵杰斯曼怎么没来
Where's Private Jesseman?
通常是他来交货
This is usually his delivery.
基地里爆发流感  长官
Flu's been tearing through the base, sir.
安排我来送货
I drew the short straw.
名单上没有你
I don't see you on the list.
你的指挥官应该提交人员变动表
Your C.O. should have submitted a change of personnel form.
你确定他没提交吗
You sure he didn't?
回基地得开一个小时的车
It's an hour's drive back to the base.
你刷新一下无线或什么的吧
Can't you refresh your Wi-Fi or something?
好了
There you are.
还给你  大兵
As you were, private.
多谢  长官
Thank you, sir.
传输完毕
我进来了
I'm in.
25分钟后撤离
25 minutes till extraction.
收到
Roger that.
大楼监控摄像机用的是闭合网络
Facilities cameras are on a closed network.
要是帮我找到主机  我就能打开
If you can give me access to the mainframe, I can open it up.
-我这就去  -奥利弗...
- I'm on my way. - Oliver...
如果你不能按时到达撤离点
If you don't make it to the extraction point--
我会成功的  还会带上他
I'll make it, and I won't be alone.
在这里休息一晚
明天再处理你
你会说英文吗
You speak English?
会
Yes.
你的口音  你是美国人
Your accent... you are American.
也许很久以前吧
Yeah, maybe once upon a time,
但我现在更享受
But, uh, now I'm more just enjoying
俄罗斯带给我的一切
everything that Russia has to offer.
感觉得出来
Yes. I can smell that.
你指责我
You judge me?
你也被关在这牢房里
You're in this cell, too.
没错  我老板很快就会纠正这个错误
Yes. A mistake my boss will correct very soon.
你是说康士坦丁・科瓦吗
You mean Konstantin Kovar?
你怎么知道这个名字
How do you know that name?
正如我知道你叫彼得・弗里德金
Same way that I know your name's Pyotr Friedkin,
正如我知道你帮科瓦洗黑钱
Same way I know that you launder money for Kovar,
同样我还知道
Same way that I know
这就是你被关在这里的原因
that's what you're doing here.
你怎么会知道  除非...
How can you know that unless...
你是兄弟会的人
Are you Bratva?
别怪我朋友
他过敏
他没事的
He's fine.
我是兄弟会的人
I am Bratva,
你要把我想知道的一切
and you are gonna tell me everything
都告诉我
that I want to know.
轮到你去巡查
Your turn to run system check.
我去上厕所
I'm gonna hit the head.
别碰我的球
Don't touch my ball.
兄弟  搞什么呢
Dude, what the hell?
转调器装好了
Transponder's in place.
收到  我看到画面了
Roger that. I've got eyes now.
我给你指出约翰牢房的路线
I'll walk you to Johnny's cell.
我来的不是时候吗
Hey. Is this... uh, is this a bad time?
我压根不想知道你是怎么找到我的
Do I want to even ask how you found me?
我觉得这问题很难回答
Heh. I feel like that's a trick question.
抱歉这里很乱
Sorry about the mess.
这个真了不起
These are amazing.
花时间修补别人丢弃之物
You spend enough time with other people's castoffs,
发觉其有用的地方
you find ways to make something useful out of them.
我父亲以前总是这么说
My father always used to say that.
他以前有间当铺
He owned a pawn shop.
在南摩尔路吧
On Southmoor Road, right?
你怎么知道
How'd you know?
上周  你和奥利弗说你加入绿箭团队
Last week, you told Oliver that you had joined the team
是为了纪念你父亲
to honor your father.
当你退出时
When you quit...
我想找出更多你放弃的原因
I wanted to find out more about what you were giving up.
1990年8月2日至1991年2月28日期间
美国为首的由34个国家组成的联军和伊拉克之间发生的一场局部战争
你父亲曾是海湾战争的一名老兵
Your father was a Gulf War veteran,
第一海军陆战队第二营
2nd battalion, 1st marines,
但他不是因此而成为英雄的  对吧
but that's not what made him a hero, was it?
不是
No.
他穿着你修补的旧货
He wore your rags,
就像他的祖父一样  也叫罗里
like his father before him, whose name was also Rory.
这是个需要背负的巨大传承
That's a big legacy to live up to.
而我要背负的是发生在海文洛克的不幸
Mine is going to be what happened to Havenrock.
我余下人生中的每一天
I'm gonna have to live with that
都得背负这件事
every day for the rest of my life,
明知无法补救
Knowing that I cannot fix it
明知那不会是我犯下的
and knowing that it's not the last mistake
最后一个错误
that I'm ever going to have to make.
我还是不知道我是否能
I still don't know if I can--
和一个提醒着你自己失去了什么的人
Work side by side with someone who's a reminder
肩并肩一起做事
of what you lost.
我明白
I understand.
正如你提醒着我做了什么
Just like you're a reminder of what I did,
我知道两件事不一样
and I-I know they're not the same thing.
但是我们的目的一样
We both want the same thing,
能够接受所发生的事
to be able to live with what's happened
我们才能继续活下去
so that we can move forward.
柯蒂斯
查到丘奇的情报
是柯蒂斯
It's Curtis.
对不起
I am so sorry,
可我们真的很需要你帮忙
and we could really use you.
现在不行
I can't right now.
对不起
I'm sorry.
如果你改变主意  来找我们
If you change your mind, well, we're here.
1138号牢房
Cell 1138,
右侧  左边数第三间
right side, third from the left.
他不在里面
He's not here.
给我一分钟  我扫描一下信号
Give me a minute while I scan the feeds.
糟了
Oh, no.
怎么了
What?
他们把他转到囚区去了
They moved him into gen pop.
你一旦走进去  你们俩都出不来
You go in there, neither of you are getting out.
告诉我  他什么时候会回自己的牢房
Talk to me. When's he coming back to his cell?
预计路线 八百米
我们时间来不及
Outside our window.
如果那些宪兵反应过来  要做的第一件事
If those MPs wake up, the first thing they're gonna do
就是把约翰和所有的囚犯
is move John and all the other prisoners
转移到更安全的地方  我们就没机会了
to a more secure location, and we lose our shot.
预计路线 八百米
终止行动  我们要撤离
Abort. We're blown.
告诉我科瓦在哪
Tell me where I can find Kovar.
你觉得比起他  我更怕你吗
You think you scare me more than him?
不  但他没和你一起关在这里
No, but he's not locked up in here with you.
我和你一起
I am.
你不会当着他们的面杀我的
You wouldn't kill me in front of all of them.
我碰都不会碰你
I'm not gonna lay a finger on you.
艾丽莎我就不敢担保了
Same can't be said for Alisa.
或者等你妻子玛雅去芭蕾舞课
Or maybe I'll visit your wife Maya
接艾丽莎时  我会去看看她
when she's picking up Alisa from ballet.
有人会死
Somebody is gonna die.
可以是科瓦  或你妻子  也可以是你孩子
It can be Kovar, it can be your wife, it can be your child,
我要你做出选择
but I need you to choose
而且要快
and do it quickly.
科瓦疑心很重  小心
Kovar is very paranoid, careful.
我们从没见过他本人
We never meet in person,
只远程联络
Only remotely.
怎么远程联络
Remotely? How?
一个电子情报点  暗网
A digital dead drop, the dark web.
IP地址是什么
What's the IP address?
What is the IP address?
108.166.7.161.
如果你的信息有误
If this information is incorrect,
你家人会遭殃的
Your family will suffer.
一个美国人怎么变成了
How does an American become this...this...
兄弟会恶魔
Bratva devil?
我不知道
I don't know.
发生了什么事
怎么回事
他摔倒了
一定是喝醉了
把人抬出去
是时候了  金发妞  我们现在可以出发了吗
About time, blondie. Can we go now?
首先  那不是我的名字
First of all, not my name.
其次  你查到丘奇的位置了吗
Second, were you able to locate Church on your recon?
没有  但是街道摄像头捕捉到了他
No, but street cams actually picked him up,
我们知道他在行动
So we know he's on the move.
只是不知道他要去哪
We just don't know where he's moving to.
位置
北纬87.75754
东经12.85753
不知道丘奇的最终目标
We can't go after Church without knowing
我们也没法追他
his endgame first.
听起来像是什么也不做的借口
Sounds like an excuse to sit around and do nothing.
不是什么都不做
Not nothing.
你在用投影算法
You're cross-plotting Church's prior locations
交叉分析丘奇之前的位置
into a projection algorithm.
你小学时应该经常被打
You probably got beat up in grade school a lot.
初中也是
And junior high.
基于丘奇以往的路线
Ok. Based on Church's route, I'm calculating
位置  米尔路18号  准确度  86%
他有86%的可能性去米尔路18号
an 86% likelihood he's going to 18 mill road.
怎么听着这么熟
Why does that sound so familiar?
因为我们刚才就在那儿
Because we were just there
交出塞吉奥
to hand over sergio.
陆军作战队被困在那里
That's where the ACU's bunkered.
丘奇要除掉他们
Church is gonna take them out.
蒙特斯  别瞎搞了
Montes, quit screwing around.
报告站长  我是C区牢房的甘斯
Station chief, this is Gans from cell block C.
发现黄色警报情况
Ave a code yellow situation.
启动紧急封锁
Initiate immediate lockdown
将所有囚犯送回牢房
and have all prisoners return to their cells.
我不要惹丘奇
I'm not rolling on Church.
你觉得你比他更可怕吗
You think you scare me more than him?
不
No...
但是他不在
But he's not here with you.
我在
I am.
你才不会打我
You're not gonna put a beating on me.
你是检察官
You're a D.A.
没错  没听说过吗
Yeah. Haven't you heard?
这座城市的正义由治安维持者维护
All of the justice in this city comes from vigilantes.
有消息称丘奇在计划着
Word on the street is is that Church's planning something,
干一大票
something big.
告诉我情况
You tell me what it is,
就是他蹲监狱
and he'll be the one in those cuffs
而不是你
instead of you.
你要我信你
You're talking about the trust.
你阻止不了的
Oh, you can't stop it, man.
你根本敌不过他
Can't even come close.
发生了什么事
What the hell is going on?
丘奇
Church.
至少我们现在确定了丘奇在哪
At least we definitely know where Church is now.
迪・安格罗[黑人歌手]说得对
D'Angelo's right.
我们得解决他
We got to put him down.
对抗他们  没有奥利弗
Against that? Without Oliver?
不行  我们现在缺人手
No. We're sh-- shorthanded as it is.
你害怕了
You scared?
没有  但是我不蠢
No, but I'm not stupid either.
艾薇说得对
Evie's right.
我不能让你们去送死
I'm not sending you guys out there just to get slaughtered.
感谢你的信任
Thanks for the vote of confidence.
你看到了你要面对的情况
You saw what you're up against, ok?
这和训练中不一样
This isn't some drill where you take down
不是对付小歹徒或毒贩
a petty thug or drug dealer.
这是实战  真正的危险
This is real, ok, with real stakes.
你们三个也许会牺牲
The three of you could die out there.
这要我们自己决定
That's something we get to decide for ourselves,
不是吗
isn't it?
我不知道其他人怎么想的
I mean, I don't know about everyone else,
但我不是为了保命才加入这个团队
but I didn't join this team to stay safe.
好吧  我们投个票吧
Ok. Why don't we take a vote?
同意的人...
All those in favor...
我们都投赞成票  金发妞
We're all gonna say yes, blondie.
天  那不是我的名字
God. That's not my name.
好吧  去吧  注意安全
Good. Ok. Go. Do not die.
黄色警报
Code yellow.
将所有犯人押回牢房
Return all prisoners to their cells.
黄色警报
Code yellow.
将所有犯人押回牢房
Return all prisoners to their cells.
约翰  还好吗
Hey, John. What's new?
我不越狱  我告诉过莱拉
I'm not doing this. I told Lyla.
你可以之后再向我们发火
Yeah. You can yell at us later,
但现在我们赶时间
but right now, we're on a bit of a clock.
你有听我说的话吗
Are you even hearing me right now?
我一点都不想越狱
I don't want anything to do with this.
宪兵们几分钟后做清点
The MPs are gonna do a count in a few minutes.
我想他们只希望看到这里一个人
My guess is they're only expecting to find one person in here.
真的吗  你就这样威胁我
Really? So that's your play, blackmail?
要么按你说的做  要么害你也被抓
Do what you say, or you get caught in here, too?
你是我兄弟  约翰
You're my brother, John.
你我同甘共苦
What happens to you happens to me.
奥利弗...
Oliver...
我杀了自己弟弟
I killed my brother.
我参军以求改变
I went to the army to change,
却没能改变
and I haven't changed.
我知道  好吗
I know, all right,
我也知道你觉得现在是赎罪
and I know that you think this is your penance for that.
奥利弗  还不止这样
Oliver, it's not just that.
我信任安迪
I trusted Andy.
即便你叫我提防他  我还是信任他
Even when you told me not to, I trusted him,
但劳蕾尔死了
and now Laurel's dead.
我需要你  团队需要你  这座城需要你
I need you, the team needs you, the city needs you.
我不是说你不该赎罪
I'm not saying you shouldn't do your penance.
你或许是该赎罪
You probably should,
但要像个勇士一样去赎罪
but do it as Spartan.
盒子里是什么
What's in the box?
是反分子化合物
It's an antimolecular compound,
从理论上说  它应该能噬穿任何物体
and theoretically, it should eat through anything.
我也不打算问你从哪弄来的
Not gonna ask you how you got your hands on this.
你回来找我了
Hey. You came back for me,
虽然我叫你别来
even against my wishes.
我猜我也没怎么变
I guess I haven't changed that much either.
或许我该为这个赎罪
Maybe that's what I have to do my penance for.
你刚才用的东西以后绝对能派上大用场
That toy of yours is definitely coming in handy.
前提是莱拉一直盯着超能力联合调查组
Project that Lyla's been keeping an eye on for ARGUS.
早该料到有她的份
Should have known she'd be helping out.
告诉约翰以后再谢我
Tell Johnny he can thank me later.
你们继续走
You've got to keep moving.
沿地下层向北走200米然后爬上去
Follow the sublevel north 200 meters, then climb up.
那...那是什么声音
What--what is it?
通讯中断了
Comm's being jammed.
不不不
No, no, no.
还有别的出口吗
Hey. Is there another way out of here?
介意在你死前  解开我的手铐吗
Mind uncuffing me before they kill you?
如果你要炸掉那面墙
Hey. If that's for taking out the wall,
我们还没出去就会被炸死
the blast will kill us before we can get out.
我们离得太近了
We're in too tight.
-相信我  -是啊  相信一个面目狰狞的...
- Trust me. ?- Yeah, says the creepy-looking--?
你到底是什么鬼东西
What the hell are you anyways?
就位  炸吧
I'm in place. Blow it.
抱歉炸了你们的大楼
Sorry we blew up your building.
快点
Come on!
我们上去
We're going up.
然后呢
Then what?
走哪边  守望者
Which way, overwatch?
在走廊尽头右转
Take a right ?at the end of that hallway.?
应该是个消防出口
It should be a fire exit.
你们出去以后就能轻松回家了
If you go through there, you're home free easy.
没那么轻松
Not so easy.
破烂王  掩护我
Rags, cover me.
走走走
Go! Go, go!
走
Go!
扶他起来
Get him up.
起来
Come on.
我或许应该直接打死你们
I probably should just shoot you,
但是...
But...
你们得尝点苦头
But you've earned a little suffering.
带他去安全的地方
Get him to safety.
-但是...  -快走
- But-- - Go!
留活口
Hey. Don't kill him.
他或许有点用
He may have his uses.
我们得回去救野狗
We've got to go back for Wild Dog.
收到  守望者  卓越先生受伤了
Copy. Overwatch, Mr. Terrific is hurt.
我们需要帮助
We could use some help.
车进站了  坚持住
Inbound. Hold on.
上车
Get in!
野狗那孩子呢
Where's the Wild Dog kid?
还在里面  跟丘奇打斗
Still inside, fighting Church.
我们得回去救他
We've got to go back for him.
不行  除非你们都想死
No. Unless you all want to die,
我们现在就得离开  就现在
We've got to go now, now!
我们不能就这样丢下他
We can't just leave him.
你们没得选  快走
You have to. Go.
上车
Come on!
-给  -这是什么
- Here. - What's this?
穿上
Just put it on.
我们走
Let's go.
狄格  你的护具
Dig, your harness.
你们两个  不许动
You two, freeze!
趴在地上  双手放在脑后
Down on the ground! Lace your fingers behind your head!
现在就照做  否则我们开枪了
Do it now, or we will shoot!
约翰  别动
John, don't move.
你暂时待在这里避风头
This place should keep you off the grid for the time being,
我们会找到一个长久的办法
until we find a permanent solution.
先做紧急的事
Hey. First things first.
不敢相信你帮我越狱
Can't believe you broke me out of prison.
你出来了就好  约翰
For better or worse, Johnny.
我想留在监狱的
Told you I wanted to stay.
我想着  如果你想要自己做决定
And I figured if you wanted to make your own decisions
你就不会结婚了
then you wouldn’t have gotten married.
你们决定救我时  费利西蒂有多生气
Ok. How mad was Felicity that you went along with this?
你怎么知道她觉得这是馊主意
How do you know she thought it was a bad idea?
我了解费利西蒂
I know Felicity.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我得走了
I have to go.
你说你没改变...
When you said you haven't changed...
那就别改变
Don't.
早上好
Dobroye utro.
在俄罗斯监狱的第一晚过得如何
How was first night in Russian prison?
弗里德金供出了情报点  现在他死了
Friedkin gave up the dead drop, and now he's dead.
任务完成
Mission accomplished.
你在讽刺  是吧
You're being sarcasm, yes?
那人不构成威胁  阿纳托利
That man wasn't a threat, Anatoly.
他不该死
He didn't deserve to die.
在兄弟会  为了达成目的一定会死人
In Bratva, there is no death without purpose.
如果弗里德金活着  他会去警告科瓦
If Friedkin living, he is warning Kovar.
如果他去警告科瓦
If he is warning Kovar,
他的情报就不会准确
his information not so good.
明白吗
Vy ponimayete?
你本可以向我解释清楚
Maybe you could have explained that to me
再派我过去
before you sent me in there.
我差点手软了
I almost didn't kill him.
但你还是杀了  为什么
But you did. Why?
因为你叫我这么做
Because you told me to.
你信任我们
You trust us.
我们也信任你
Now we trust you.
第三次测试结束
Third test over.
明白吗
You get it?
你现在是兄弟会的人了
You are Bratva now, family.
这个城市里仅剩的警界骨干
Last handful of honest cops in this city,
丘奇差点把我和他们一起干掉
and Church nearly took them out along with me.
幸好你没出事
We're just glad you're all right.
我认为这是一场公关危机
I've got to be thinking this is a PR nightmare.
发生这一系列事情  市长也失踪了
Something like this going down and the mayor's MIA.
听着  他今早打了电话
Look. He called in this morning.
他身体差不多恢复了
His health problems are almost over.
真是个好消息
That's good news.
我们  我们听说
Um, we're--we're hearing that
有一名参与救援的治安维持者
one of the, uh, Vigilantes who was part of the rescue,
没能逃出来
that he didn't make it out.
有他的消息吗
Um, any word on him?
犯罪现场小组没找到尸体
CSU hasn't found a body, so...
那么他在丘奇手上
So Church has him.
我之前一直认为
I spent most of my life thinking that
戴面具的人不可能是好人
men in masks were only capable of doing horrible things.
我的想法得改改了
I may have to reevaluate that.
奎恩来了记得告诉我
Let me know when Queen gets in.
好的
Will do.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
是的  很好
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我不是很了解那孩子  西娅
I mean, I barely knew the kid, Thea.
但并不代表你就不那么心疼
But that doesn't make it sting any less.
当然  当然是这样
Well, yeah, sure it does.
我那些年很糟糕  现在这不算什么
The year I've had, this is--this is easy.
没错  听起来确实很冷血
Yeah. I mean, cold as that sounds.
听着  我知道你为什么会问
Look. I know why you're asking, ok,
我  我很好
and I'm--I'm fine.
行
Ok.
我意思是  我就是想说
I mean, I'm--I'm--I'm just saying
如果情况不那么顺
if things ever get less easy,
我一直都会陪着你  知道吗
you know I'm here for you, right?
知道了
Noted...
我很感激
and appreciated.
好吧
Ok.
如果你用侦察卫星图像找不到任何人
What is the point of having keyhole satellite imagery
那你用那个还有什么意义
if you can't use it to find anybody?
我觉得我不是很理解
I feel like I don't understand
你说的是什么意思
half the sentences you say.
我是说  无论我怎么找
What I'm saying is that no matter how hard I try
我都找不到雷内
I cannot find Rene anywhere.
而且是我要你们把他丢下的
And I was the one who told you guys to leave him behind.
听着感觉是很困难的决定
Sounds like another impossible decision.
你是说我应该学学怎么做决定吗
Does that mean I'm supposed to get better at making them?
我是说你的决定是对的
I'm saying you were right.
如果我们要维护治安
If we're gonna do this,
就不能让罪恶感吞噬我们
we can't let guilt swallow us up.
我会帮你摆脱罪恶感
I'll keep you from doing it
只要你也这样向我承诺
if you promise the same for me.
行
Deal.
叫什么呢
So "ow" then?
没有奥利弗在
Things have really fallen apart
事情都变糟了  不是吗
without Oliver, haven't they?
好消息是我回来了
It's a good thing I'm back then.
他一直在等着我们说到他才来吧
Was he waiting for an entrance line?
不  他就是这么酷
Nope. He's just that cool.
我收到你的信息了  找到雷内了吗
I got your text. Have we found Rene?
约翰出来了吗
You get John?
是的  他很好  已经藏在蜂巢了
Yeah. He's fine. He's holed up at HIVE.
我不能丢下他
I couldn't write him off,
我们同样不能丢下雷内
and we are not gonna write off Rene.
我们会找到他
We're gonna find him,
我们要把他带回来
We're gonna bring him back...
无论他在哪
wherever he is.
醒来啦
Ah. Wakey, wakey.
哥们  我已经很久
Man, it's been a long time
没被这样绑过了
since I've been tagged like this.
谢谢了
Respect.
这是我的荣幸
Oh, my pleasure,
我向你保证  如果你给我松绑
but I promise you if you untie me
我会加倍"感谢"你的
I'll show you a hell of a lot more than respect.
哥们  你真有种
Ooh, man, you got spirit.
真让人印象深刻
And I'm duly impressed.
我会消磨你的勇气
And I'm gonna break this spirit.
我会折磨你的灵魂
I'm going to break your soul.
完事以后
And when we're finished,
假设你还活着
assuming you're still alive.
不过现在  我可不会保证
Now, I wouldn't bet no money on that, though.
回去跟绿箭侠一起共事的你
This gonna be very little of you left for
不会再完整了
the Green Arrow to work with.
接着电
Light him up.
一键收藏网盘资源生活大爆炸 吸血鬼日记
西部世界 谍网 超女
美剧资源应有尽有
扫码即刻关注
Zimuzu特别推荐
马上关注微信人人美剧（rrmjapp）